question_data_film = [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, 'Chewbacca' is an Ewok.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The movie 'The Nightmare before Christmas' was all done with physical objects.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004's 'The Aviator&quot'.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies "
                     "Interstellar and The Martian.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional "
                     "computing power instead of batteries.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during"
                     " and after filming.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherfucker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber"
                     " during the filming of Star Wars.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate"
                     " the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                          "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
